http://www.smokingstopshere.com/privacy-policy

Select LanguageAfrikaansAlbanianArabicArmenianAzerbaijaniBasqueBelarusianBulgarianCatalanChinese (Simplified)Chinese (Traditional)CroatianCzechDanishDutchEnglishEstonianFilipinoFinnishFrenchGalicianGeorgianGermanGreekHaitian CreoleHebrewHindiHungarianIcelandicIndonesianIrishItalianJapaneseKoreanLatvianLithuanianMacedonianMalayMalteseNorwegianPersianPolishPortugueseRomanianRussianSerbianSlovakSlovenianSpanishSwahiliSwedishThaiTurkishUkrainianUrduVietnameseWelshYiddish
Cigarette smoking increases your risk of severe illness from COVID-19.
Maryland Department of Health InfoCDC Info
It's Free. It's Confidential.
IT WORKS!
24 Hours, 7 Days A Week
Getting Started4 Steps to Quitting Smoking in Maryland1-800-QUIT-NOW
– Maryland Smoking Cessation SupportText SupportWeb SupportMediaSuccess StoriesFind Local ResourcesAlleganyAnne ArundelBaltimore CityBaltimore CountyCalvertCarolineCarrollCecilCharlesDorchesterFrederickGarrettHarfordHowardKentMontgomeryPrince George’sQueen Anne’sSomersetSt. Mary’sTalbotWashingtonWicomicoWorcesterResources for ProvidersBehavioral Health Provider ResourcesFax-to-AssistEnroll Now
Privacy Policy
Home/Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
admin
2017-07-03T10:12:58+00:00
Terms of Use / Policy Notice
This Web site is provided as a public service by the Maryland Department of Health.
Site User Statistics Reporting
Of the information we learn about you from your visit to http://www.smokingstopshere.com, we may store the following:
The domain name from which you access the Internet;
The date and time;
The Internet address of the Web site from which you linked directly to our site;
The name of the file or the words you searched; and
The browser you used to access our site.
This information is used to (1) measure the number of visitors to the site’s various sections and (2) identify system performance or problem areas.
We also use this information to help us expand the coverage of the site to assist users in finding health information.
Data Collection
If we request personal information from you, we are obligated under state law to provide you with the following information:
The purpose for which the personal information is collected;
Any specific consequences to the person for refusal to provide the personal information;
Your right to inspect, amend, or correct personal records, if any;
Whether the personal information is generally available for public inspection; and
Whether the personal information is made available or transferred to or shared with any entity other than the official custodian.
We do not give, share, sell or transfer any personal information collected on this site to a third party, unless otherwise specified. User information will not be used for commercial use.
You are not required to provide information to us. If we request information and you refuse to provide it to us, your refusal will not be held against you or prejudice our relationship with you.
When inquiries are e-mailed to us, we store the question and the e-mail address information so that we can respond electronically. Unless otherwise required by statute, we do not identify publicly who sends questions or comments to our Web site. We will not obtain information that will allow us to personally identify you when you visit our site, unless you chose to provide such information to us.
Information that you consider confidential should not be sent to us over the Internet.
Removal
If you would like to remove yourself from our mailing list, please send an e-mail message to info@smokingstopshere.com.
Correcting or Updating Your Information
If you wish to correct, update, or otherwise modify the information that you have provided for a mailing list, please send an e-mail message to info@smokingstopshere.com.
Disclaimer of Liability
For documents available from this site, the Maryland Department of Health does not warrant or assume any legal liability or responsibility for the accuracy, completeness, or usefulness of any information, apparatus, product, or process disclosed.
Disclaimer of Endorsement
General
The Maryland Department of Health does not endorse or recommend any commercial products, processes, or services. The views and opinions of authors expressed on the Smoking Stops Here Web site do not necessarily state or reflect those of the Maryland Department of Health, and they may not be used for advertising or product endorsement purposes.
External Links
Smoking Stops Here provides links to other Internet sites only for the convenience of World Wide Web users. The Maryland Department of Health is not responsible for the availability or content of these external sites, nor does the Department endorse, warrant, or guarantee the products, services, or information described or offered at these other Internet sites.
Medical Information It is not the intention of Smoking Stops Here to provide specific medical advice, but rather to provide users with access to general information to facilitate a better understanding of public health issues. Specific medical advice will not be provided, and the Maryland Department of Health urges you to consult with an appropriate, qualified medical provider for diagnosis and for answers to your personal questions.
Intellectual Property
Copyright © 2006-2014 Maryland Department of Health
This Web site is protected by copyright as a collective work and/or compilation, pursuant to U.S. copyright laws, international conventions, and other laws. Unless otherwise indicated, the Content (including, but not limited to, graphic images, buttons, layout, trademarks, logos, text, and other materials) contained in this Web site is the exclusive property of the Maryland Department of Health and/or its related, affiliated, and subsidiary organizational units, or its third-party licensors.
If notification of use is provided, permission is granted for use of the site’s information only for noncommercial, scientific, educational, or personal purposes. (Use of the site’s graphics or images is prohibited unless otherwise indicated.) Please send notification of use to info@smokingstopshere.com.
Questions about Maryland-Smoking Stops Here policies should be sent to info@smokingstopshere.com.
